A racing second hand, a shooting comet!
عقرب دقائق مسرِع، مُذنّب ساقط
Conan's logic will moisten hearts dried by modern society!
ستبلل استنتاجات كونان القلوب !التي جفّفها المجتمع الحديث
Today's proof is quite unique! Let's change our way of thinking!
دليل اليوم فريد! لنغيّر منظور تفكيرنا
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
The 3rd Set of Fingerprints Murder Case
جريمة قتل البصمة الثالثة
I'm done with my bath, Ran-neechan!
انتهيت من الاستحمام يا ران-نيتشان
Are you busy tomorrow, Conan-kun?
أأنت متفرّغ غداً يا كونان-كن؟
No, I have no plans. Why?
أجل، لا جدول محدد لديّ. ما الأمر؟
One of Dad's friends just called
اتّصل أحد معارف أبي للتو
and invited us over for a BBQ tomorrow afternoon!
ودعانا لحفلة شواء ظهيرة الغد
He's a friend of yours?
أحد معارفك؟
His name's Teraoka-san.
اسمه تيراوكا-سان
He really watched over me when I was a police detective.
اعتنى بي عندما كنتُ محقّقاً في الشرطة لعامين
Now he's chief inspector of Investigation Section ♪4.
منصبه كبير المفتّشين في قسم التحقيق الرابع الآن
That's the group in charge of handling gangs! I'll come!
!هذا القسم المكلّف بقضايا العصابات! سآتي
Real police detectives have lots of interesting stories!
قد يكون لدى محقّقي الشرطة الحقيقيين الكثير من القصص المثيرة
I can't wait!
!أتحرّق شوقاً
Teraoka
تيراوكا
You'd always say my logic was wrong,
كنتَ تقول دائماً أن استنتاجي خاطئ
but then you'd wind up being wrong yourself!
!وفي النهاية يتّضح أنك أنت المخطئ
He's still like that.
لا يزال هكذا
Now you're a famous detective! To be honest, it's hard to believe!
!أصبحتَ متحرّياً مشهوراً الآن أجد صعوبة في تصديق الأمر بصراحة
Please give me some credit...
...لا تحرجني يا سينباي
Here, have some-- Huh?
هاك شراباً... ماذا؟
You haven't had a drop to drink! That's not like you!
!لم تشرب البتّة! ليس هذا من طباعك
I'm off duty, but there's no telling what might come up.
أنا خارج العمل، لكن لا تعلم ما قد يطرأ أبداً
This is an awesome car! It must be expensive!
!هذه سيّارة مذهلة يا عمّ! لا بد أنّها باهظة الثمن
Cars are my only hobby, so I spend my money on them.
،السيّارات هي هوايتي الوحيدة لذا أنفق مالي عليها
Say, Ran-chan. Did you have something to do today?
أخبريني يا ران-تشان، أكان لديك مخطّط ما اليوم؟
Nothing at all!
كلا، مُطلقاً
I'm sorry for calling out of the blue!
أعتذر على مباغتتكم
He suddenly decided last night and all...
فقد اتّخذ قراره فجأةً البارحة
At 9:00, he left his room and said, "I'm bringing Mori over tomorrow!"
"غادر غرفته عند التاسعة وقال "سأدعو موري غداً
He normally plans things out well in advance...
يميل للتخطيط أكثر في العادة
I just thought it would be nice...
خطر لي أنّها ستكون مناسبة جميلة
Hello?
مرحباً
Maybe something happened?
أوقعت حادثة؟
What?!
!ماذا؟
Where are you?!
أين أنت؟
Alright! I'll be right there!
!حسناً، سآتي فوراً
I won't tell anyone! I'll come alone! Alright?!
لن أخبر أحداً! سآتي بمفردي، واضح؟
I'll be waiting!
!سأنتظرك
Sorry. I'll be back soon.
آسف، سأغادر قليلاً
Did something happen?
أوقع أمرٌ ما؟
That was Matsuyama, a gang leader.
كان ذلك ماتسوياما، زعيم عصابة
Apparently, he accidentally killed someone last night.
يبدو أنّه قتل شخصاً بالخطأ البارحة
What?!
ماذا؟
He's wanted to change his ways, and I've been giving him advice.
أراد تصحيح مساره، وكنتُ أساعده بالنصح
I'm going to convince him to turn himself in.
سأذهب لإقناعه بتسليم نفسه
All by yourself? That's not a good idea.
بمفردك يا سينباي؟ ليست فكرةً حسنة
If he were to run away, you'd be held responsible!
!ستقع عليك المسؤولية إن هرب
And it's dangerous! You should contact HQ and--
...كما أنّ الأمر خطر! عليك الاتّصال بالمركز و
I can't! I promised I would go alone and tell no one!
لا يمكنني! وعدته أن آتي بمفردي !وألّا أخبر أحداً
But you're off duty, and without a gun--
...لكنّك خارج وقت عملك، وبلا مسدّس
I don't need a gun! He called me out of trust!
!لا أحتاج مسدّساً! فقد استدعاني لثقته بي
I can't betray that!
!لا يمكنني خيانة ذلك
Then I'm coming with you!
!سأرافقك إذاً
What?!
!ماذا؟
Otherwise, I'll call Inspector Megure!
!وإلّا سأضطر للاتصال بالمفتّش ميغوري
Why, you...
...أنت
Alright, fine. But only I'll meet him! Got that?!
حسناً، لا بأس. لكني سألتقيه وحدي، مفهوم؟
Yes. So where is he?
أجل، أين المكان؟
Kowan Wharf, Warehouse 13.
رصيف كوان، المستودع 13
I'll get my jacket. Wait by the car.
سأجلب معطفي، انتظر عند السيّارة
I'll get your jacket!
سأجلب أنا معطفك
No! You just stay here!
!كلا! ابقي هنا فحسب
What's taking him so long?
...تأخّر
Sorry. It took a while to find the key.
آسف، استغرق البحث عن المفتاح وقتاً
What was that sound?
ما كان ذلك الصوت؟
Could it have been?!
...ما كان ذلك الصوت بالضبط؟ أيمكن
Will Dad be all right after having all that alcohol?!
...هل سيكون أبي بخير؟ شرب الكثير من الساكي
Ran-neechan! Let's go to Kowan Wharf too!
!ران-نيتشان، لنذهب لرصيف كوان أيضاً
You're worried about him, aren't you?! I'll get a taxi!
!أنتِ قلقة عليه، صحيح؟ سأوقف سيّارة أجرة
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Dad...
...أبي
Kowan Wharf
رصيف كوان
What are you doing here?!
!لمَ أتيتما هنا؟
Where's Teraoka-san?
أين تيراوكا-سان؟
Back there.
في الخلف هناك
He told me to wait here.
أخبرني بالانتظار مكاني
Let's check it out, too!
لنذهب لتفقّد الوضع
What are you saying?! That would put him in--
...ما الذي تقوله؟! سيضعه ذلك في
Dad!
!أبي
He doesn't have a gun!
!لا يحمل سينباي مسدّساً
Meaning the other guy does!
...ما يعني أنّ الرجل الآخر
Wait, Conan!
!انتظر يا كونان
Senpai...
...سينباي
So when you tried to get him to turn himself in,
عندما حاولتَ إقناع ماتسوياما بتسليم نفسه إذاً
he pulled out a gun and demanded your money and credit cards?
أخرج مسدّسه وطلب منك إخراج مالك وبطاقاتك الائتمانية؟
Yes. It seems he planned to skip the country...
أجل، يبدو أنّه كان يخطط لمغادرة البلاد من البداية
I told him he'd never get away, and that we should talk it over.
أخبرته أنّه لن يستطيع الهرب أبداً، وعلينا مناقشة الأمر
I put my hands up and walked slowly toward him.
رفعتُ ذراعيّ ومشيت نحوه ببطء
I jumped at him and tried to snatch the gun away--
...ثمّ باغتّه وحاولت سحب المسدس
--when it went off.
وانطلقت الرصاصة
It was just an unfortunate accident, Inspector Megure!
!كان حادثاً! إنّه مجرد حادث مؤسف يا مفتّش ميغوري
Who exactly did Matsuyama kill?
من الذي قتله ماتسوياما؟
I don't know his name, but he said he was a gambling client.
لا أعرف اسمه، لكنّه قال أنّه عميل قمار
And your relation with Matsuyama?
وما علاقتك بماتسوياما بالأصل؟
They had talked about him getting out of a life of crime!
!كانا يتكلمان حول إخراج ماتسوياما من حياة الجريمة
That's why he came alone to meet him!
!لذا أتى سينباي للقائه بمفرده لثقته به
That was another mistake. I take full responsibility.
كانت تلك غلطة، أتحمّل المسؤولية كاملة
My judgment was too weak!
أخطأت في حكمي
Senpai...
...سينباي
If my theory is correct, this was no accident. It was a murder!
إن أصاب استنتاجي، فلم يكن ذلك حادثاً !بل جريمة قتل
Teraoka-san is the killer!
!المجرم هو تيراوكا-سان بلا شك
But there's no proof of it!
!لكن لا دليل لديّ
Here you are.
تفضّل
Thank you.
شكراً لك
You've probably already seen on TV or in the papers,
لعلّك عرفت من التلفاز أو الصحف سلفاً
but Matsuyama's victim was indeed a gambling client.
لكن الضحيّة التي قتلها ماتسوياما كان عميل قمار حقّاً
The murder happened around 8:00, two nights ago,
وقعت الجريمة عند الثامنة مساءً قبل ليلتين
and the weapon was a knife, not a gun...
وكان السلاح سكّيناً، وليس مسدّساً
That's right. We still don't know why he didn't use a gun,
أجل، لا نزال نجهل لمَ لم يستعمل مسدّساً
but it looks like a gambling debt was at the root of it all.
لكن يبدو أنّ دين القمار كان أساس النزاع
What about Teraoka-senpai's involvement?
ماذا عن تورّط تيراوكا سينباي إذاً؟
A formal decision is forthcoming, but he did go alone
لم يُتّخذ قرار رسميّ بعد، لكنه ذهب بمفرده
and allowed Matsuyama to die, accident or not...
وتسبب بموت ماتسوياما، كان حادثاً أم لا
He'll probably lose a few months' pay.
سيفقد مرتّب بضعة أشهر غالباً
I see...
...هكذا إذاً
Which means nobody doubts Teraoka-san's testimony...
ما يعني أنّ لا أحد يشكّ بكلام تيراوكا-سان
Oh, there is one thing we've kept from the media--
بالمناسبة، هناك ما أخفيناه عن الإعلام بشأن حادثة الأمس
we found three sets of fingerprints on the gun.
وجدنا 3 بصمات مختلفة على المسدّس
Three sets?!
ثلاث بصمات؟
One is Matsuyama's, and another is Inspector Teraoka's.
إحداها لماتسوياما، والأخرى للمفتّش تيراوكا
We've determined that his prints got there during the struggle,
حددنا أن بصماته سببها منازعة المسدّس مع ماتسوياما
but we don't know who the others belong to.
لكن لا نزال نجهل صاحب البصمة الثالثة
Maybe from someone in Matsuyama's gang?
لعلّه أحد أفراد عصابة ماتسوياما
No. We got all their prints, but none matched up.
كلا، لدينا كلّ بصماتهم، لكن لم نجد أيّ تطابق
Maybe an unrelated arms dealer?
ربما لتاجر أسلحة غير ذي علاقة إذاً؟
We've considered that too, but we don't have any leads.
فكّرنا بذلك أيضاً، لكن لا نملك أيّ خيوط
Who does the third set belong to? If that gun's owner is who I suspect it is...
لمن هي البصمة الثالثة؟ إن كان ...مالك المسدّس هو من أشتبه به
Inspector! You told Teraoka-san about those fingerprints, right?!
حضرة المفتّش! أخبرتَ تيراوكا-سان عن أمر البصمات الثلاث، صحيح؟
How did he look at the time?!
كيف كانت ملامحه آنذاك؟
Now that you mention it, he seemed extremely shocked.
كيف كانت؟ صحيح... بدا أنّه مصدوم
No doubt about it! Matsuyama was shot by Teraoka-san!
!لا شكّ في الأمر! أطلق تيراوكا-سان على ماتسوياما
The third set of prints is the proof!
!البصمة الثالثة هي الدليل
Teraoka residence.
مرحباً، منزل تيراوكا
Oh, Inspector Megure!
!مفتّش ميغوري
I'd like to discuss yesterday's incident.
أريد مناقشة أمر معك بخصوص حادثة الأمس
That was weird for Inspector Megure to ask me
من الغريب أنّ المفتّش ميغوري طلب منّي
to come to Teraoka-senpai's house at this hour!
!القدوم لمنزل تيراوكا سينباي في وقت كهذا
And me and Conan-kun! I wonder if something happened...
منّي وكونان-كن أيضاً! أوقع أمرٌ ما؟
And I called the inspector using the old man's voice!
واتّصلت بالمفتّش باستعمال صوت العمّ
Everything's all set!
!كلّ شيء جاهز
I didn't know the inspector had called you here too...
لم أعلم أنّ المفتّش ميغوري استدعاكم كذلك
Please have a seat.
تفضّلوا بالجلوس
To be honest, I don't know why he called us here, either.
لا أعرف لمَ استدعانا أيضاً بصراحة
Say, Miss.
يا عمّة
There's a show I wanna see...
هناك مسلسل أريد مشاهدته
There's a TV you can watch in the spare room upstairs.
يوجد تلفاز في غرفة شاغرة في الطابق الثاني، يمكنك المشاهدة هناك
Yaiba Punch!
!لكمة يايبا
This room is for when we have guests over.
هذه الغرفة لمبيت الضيوف عند زيارتهم
You and Ran should come spend the night sometime.
عليك أن تبيت وران-تشان هنا من حين لآخر
Yeah!
!أجل
So this is Teraoka-san's room.
...هذه غرفة تيراوكا-سان إذاً
There's only one missing...
...يوجد واحد ناقص
It's in the trash?!
في القمامة؟
A felt rag?
لُباد؟
Smells of oil. Did he use the inside of this to--
...رائحة زيت، أيمكن أنّ تيراوكا-سان وضع هنا
So what did you have to say, Mori-kun?
ما الذي أردت قوله إذاً يا موري-كن؟
You're the one who had something to say...
أنت من قال أنّ لديه ما يريد قوله
What?! You called me and said you had something to say!
ما الذي تتكلّم عنه؟! أنت من اتّصل !وقال أنّه يريد قول شيء
But the one who called me was--
...لكن من اتّصل بي
Here we go again...
...مُجدداً
Very well. Let us forget the details and get down to business.
حسناً، لنترك التفاصيل جانباً وندخل في صلب الموضوع
But first, please have a seat, madam. You too, Ran.
لكن أوّلاً، هلّا جلستِ من فضلك يا آنسة؟ أنت أيضاً يا ران
Teraoka-senpai. You killed Matsuyama, didn't you?
تيراوكا سينباي، قمتَ بقتل ماتسوياما، صحيح؟
I never expected you to say that! I see you haven't changed one bit!
!تباغتني بكلام كهذا! أرى أنّك لم تتغير أبداً
When you met Matsuyama, you hit him with a knockout blow,
عندما التقيتَ ماتسوياما، ضربته وأفقدته وعيه
put the gun in his hand, aimed it at his chest, and pulled the trigger.
،ثمّ وضعت المسدّس في يده وجّهته نحو صدره وأطلقت النار
Am I wrong?
ألستُ محقّاً؟
Ridiculous! What kind of joke is this, Mori?
يا للسخافة! أيّ مزحة هذه يا موري؟
First, when you invited us to the BBQ yesterday,
بدايةً، عندما دعوتنا للشواء بالأمس
you didn't take even a single sip of beer.
لم تتناول حتّى رشفة واحدة من الجعّة
I already told you--
...أخبرتك وقتها
Yes. Just as you said, even off-duty officers don't know
...أجل، حتّى الشرطة خارج العمل لا يعرفون
when they might be called in.
متى قد يُستدعون كما قلت
So you refrained from drinking. I thought so, too.
لذا امتنعتَ عن الشراب، ذلك ما اعتقدتُه أيضاً
However, you were very intent on checking the time.
لكنّك كنت تتفقد الساعة باستمرار لسببٍ ما
Perhaps because you knew when Matsuyama would call you?
ربما لأنّك كنت تعرف متى سيتّصل ماتسوياما بك؟
That's why you left your phone on your belt and didn't drink.
لذا تركت هاتفك على حزام بنطالك ولم تشرب
I always have my phone on me! In case I get an emergency call!
أحمل هاتفي معي دوماً! في حال أتاني نداء طوارئ
Do you have it now?
أهو بحوزتك الآن؟
It's in my room now, but normally it's--
...أنا في غرفتي الآن، لكن عادةً
Next, when you spoke with Matsuyama on the phone,
تالياً، عندما تكلّمت مع ماتسوياما على الهاتف
you whispered at first but then started to shout!
همست بدايةً، لكنك بدأت برفع صوتك فجأة
What?!
!ماذا؟
Where are you?! Alright! I'll be right there!
أين أنت؟
Almost as if to let us hear what was being discussed.
كما لو كنتَ تحاول اطلاعنا على ما يتمّ قوله
Then, even though you were in a hurry, when I asked you about it,
...ثم رغم أنّك كنت في عجلة، عندما سألتُك عن الأمر
you purposely stopped and explained the call in great detail.
توقفت مكانك وشرحت المكالمة بإسهاب
That was Matsuyama, a gang leader.
كان ذلك ماتسوياما، زعيم عصابة
Apparently, he accidentally killed someone last night.
يبدو أنّه قتل شخصاً بالخطأ البارحة
But half of what you said was a lie.
لكن نصف ما قلتَه كان كذبة
I think he really called you about his murder the night before.
أظنّه اتصل بك بشأن الجريمة ليلة البارحة في الواقع
You then made arrangements with him.
اتّفقت معه آنذاك
One was to call you at 12:00 the following day.
كان عليه أن يتّصل بك اليوم التالي عند 12:00
So the person he talked to was...
...الشخص الذي كان يتكلّم معه وقتها إذاً
Actually him, during the whispering.
كان نفسه أثناء الهمس
He acted the rest out by himself.
والباقي تمثيل فرديّ
The caller had probably hung up by then.
كان المتّصل قد أغلق المكالمة بالفعل
Then, anticipating I would suggest going together,
ثمّ، بتوقعك أنّي سأطلب أن نذهب معاً
he said he would meet Matsuyama alone.
قلتَ أنّك ستلتقي ماتسوياما بمفردك
What for?
لمَ؟
So that I would vouch that you met him unarmed.
كي أشهد أنّك ذهبت له بلا سلاح
That's why you needed me near you when he called.
لذا كنت تحتاج لأن أكون بالجوار عندما يكلّمك
He suddenly decided last night and all...
فقد اتّخذ قراره فجأةً البارحة
At 9:00, he left his room and said, "I'm bringing Mori over tomorrow!"
"غادر غرفته عند التاسعة وقال "سأدعو موري غداً
In other words, I was used as part of your plan.
أي أنّي اُستغلِلت كجزء من مكيدتك
But Mori-kun! He didn't have the gun
لكن يا موري-كن، لم يكن المسدّس بحوزته
when he got out of the car at Kowan Wharf, right?
عندما غادر السيّارة عند رصيف كوان، أليس كذلك؟
It seemed that way to me, at least.
ذلك ما بدا لي على الأقل
He purposely didn't wear his jacket to make it seem that way,
تعمّد عدم ارتداء معطفه كي يبدو الأمر كذلك
despite having gone through the trouble of getting it before leaving.
رغم ذهابه لغرفته لأخذه قبل المغادرة
So where was the gun?
أين كان المسدّس إذاً؟
Attached to his right ankle.
مربوطاً بكاحله الأيمن
He had hidden the gun in his room.
كان لديه مسدّس مخبّأ في غرفته
That's why he ardently refused when his wife offered to get his jacket.
لذا رفض بنبرة حادة عندما اقترحت زوجته أن تجلب هي المعطف
No! You just stay here!
!كلا! ابقي هنا فحسب
Well? Am I wrong?
إذاً يا سينباي؟ أأنا مخطئ؟
This is all speculation; you have no proof.
كلّ ما تقوله افتراضات، لا دليل لديك
It won't hold up in court.
سيبدو متناقضاً في المحكمة
No, there is proof. The third set of fingerprints on the gun.
كلا، لديّ دليل. البصمة الثالثة التي كانت على المسدّس
The third set of fingerprints?
البصمة الثالثة؟
As we waited for you to come back out yesterday,
،بينما كنتُ أنتظر خروجك بالأمس
your wife looked uneasily up at the upstairs room.
نظرت زوجتك بقلق لغرفة الطابق الثاني
At the time, I thought she was just worried
ظننتُها كانت قلقةً وقتها لأنّك كنت ستذهب
because you were going to meet Matsuyama without a gun.
للقاء ماتسوياما دون أخذ مسدّس
But I was wrong.
لكنّي لم أصب
She was worried because you were going to meet him with a gun.
كانت قلقةً لأنّك ستلتقيه وأنت تخفي مسدّساً
In other words, she knew you had a gun hidden in your room!
ما يعني أنّها كانت تعلم بوجود مسدّس مخبّأ في غرفتك
Most likely, she found your gun by accident
...وجدته صدفةً في السابق غالباً
and picked it up without thinking.
وحملته دون تفكير
Then she quickly put it back.
ثمّ أعادته سريعاً
She probably wanted to ask about it but was too afraid to
أرادت أن تسألك على الأرجح لكن منعها الخوف
and continued to live in constant uneasiness.
وواصلت العيش مع هذا القلق المستمر
Clueless about this, you took the gun and killed Matsuyama
وفي جهلك لذلك، أخذت المسدّس وقتلت ماتسوياما
in a fake accident.
فيما جعلته يبدو حادثاً
The third set of fingerprints belonged to her.
البصمة الثالثة التي كانت على المسدّس تخصّ الزوجة
Is this true?
أهذا صحيح يا سيّدة؟
Mori-san is exactly right!
موري-سان مُحق
Misako!
!ميساكو
Would you care to explain your motive for killing Matsuyama?
هلّا فسّرت دافعك لقتلك ماتسوياما يا سينباي؟
Don't tell me he was--
...أيمكن أنّك كنت تأخذ
--paying me off. I leaked police info to him in exchange for money.
رشوة. سرّبتُ معلومات عن الشرطة له مقابل النقود
Come again?!
!ماذا؟
It was just pocket change and unimportant info at first!
كان مجرد مبلغ صغير، والمعلومات تافهة بدايةً
I grew more and more numb to it all, and before I realized it,
...لكن بدأت أفقد إحساسي شيئاً فشيئاً، وبعدما فتحتُ عيناي
I had gone beyond the point of no return.
وجدتُ أني تجاوزت نقطة العودة
Then I got a call from him at around 8:00 two nights ago!
ثمّ تلقيت اتّصالاً منه قبل ليلتين في الساعة الثامنة
He had killed someone. He wanted money to skip the country;
قتل شخصاً، وطلب منّي مالاً لمغادرة البلاد
he said if he got caught, I would go down too!
!قال أنّه سيفضحني إذا قُبض عليه
I decided to kill him then.
قرّرتُ قتله حينها
I told him I'd have the money the next day and to call me at 12:00.
أخبرته أنّي سأجهّز المال اليوم التالي وعليه أنّ يتصل بي عند الثانية عشر
I had secretly kept the gun should any such situation come up.
أخفيتُ المسدّس في حال أتى يوم كهذا وأجبرتني الظروف
The rest was all as Mori said.
الباقي كما قال موري
I apologize for my treachery.
أعتذر على خيانتي
You know how Teraoka-san hid the gun in a video case?
خبّأ تيراوكا-سان المسدّس في حافظة شريط فيديو، صحيح؟
That's--
...يوجد شيء آخر داخله
Wait, Ran!
!انتظري
Dad!
!ألقي اللوم عليهم، وليس عليّ
This is all your fault!
!هذه غلطتك
Dad!
!أبي
Don't hide those there!
!لا تخبّئها هنا
Was this man's kid abducted?!
هل اُختطف طفل هذا الرجل؟
Dad! You have a clue about the kidnapper?!
أبي! ألديك دليل عن الخاطف؟
Keita-kun is by lots of crabs and a bubble-spouting whale!
كيتا-كن عند مكان فيه الكثير !من السرطانات، وحوت ينفخ فقاعات
This license plate is fake?!
!رقم اللوحة هذا مزيّف
Oh no! Once the kidnapper gets the money, Keita-kun is--
...كلا! بعدما يأخذ الخاطف المال، كيتا-سان سوف
That's it! The crabs and the whale!
!فهمت! السرطانات والحوت
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Chairs and Tables.
كراسي وطاولات
Next episode has a slightly odd title.
عنوان الحلقة القادمة غريب نوعاً ما
What time is it? It's "twhalve" o'clock.
سلطعون